STEFAN JONČIĆ



Personal

Address
Vojvode Stepe 344/3/11b
11010 Belgrade

Phone number +381640008817

Email stefanjoncic92@gmail.com

Date of birth 21-03-1992 Place of birth

Beograd□ Driving licence

LinkedIn
https://www.linkedin.com/in/stefan-

jon%C4%8Di%C4%87-64958a86/

Interests

- Basketball
- Gyms
- Books

I have theoretical and practical knowledge in Information system technologies. Analytic ability to come the core of problem, strong organizational skills that help me meet deadlines readiness work both as a team member individually. I have theoretical and practical knowledge in Information system technologies.

I worked on some projects(I did most of if in React) and You can see my work in this https://stefan-joncic-cv.netlify.app/:)

Work experience

Frontend Developer

Apr 2023 - May 2024

Brame R&D, Nis

Worked on project written in React. It's custom CMS project where user is enabled to create multiple different templates and customize them with drag and drop functionality and styling customisation. Beside React project is build with Material UI, Redux and styled components.

Software Developer

Dec 2021 - Jun 2022

United Group B.V., Belgrade

Worked on a project written in Angular2+. Project represents web portal for user of cable provider (SBB). Beside Angular, I have worked with Material Angular, SCSS, RxJS.

Progamer

Jul 2021 - Nov 2021

Globos osiguranje, Belgrade

I have worked on internal projects written in .NET Core. One part of frontend code was done in Angular and other part in vanilla JS. Aside from different types of data manipulation inside the application I had to display data retrieved from database in Word documents and in Excel sheets.

Software Developer

Nov 2019 - Jan 2020

OXOftware d.o.o., Belgrade

I worked on implementation of software solutions and services for financial sector.

Frontend Developer

Mar 2018 - Mar 2021

Freelance

Worked on various web sites, mostly work with HTML, SCSS, JS and React.

- Create a static website using HTML, CSS and Bootstrap
- Worked on SPA using React and SCSS. Simple application with the main focus on styling and responsive behavior
- Created a SPA using React, Redux and SCSS. The application was created as a
 portal for employees to enable them easier tracking of the business inside postal
 service (tracking parcels and letters
- within districts). Used MaterialUI for several components and layout within the application
- · Develope eCommerce web site in Shopify

Education and Qualifications

Master of Science - MS

Sep 2015 - Sep 2017

University of Belgrade, Faculty of Mechanical Engineering, Belgrade

Skills

HTML5	••••
CSS3	••••
JavaScript	• • • • •
React	••••
TypeScript	• • • • •
Angular 2+	$\bullet \bullet \circ \circ \circ$